betarecords.com 2012-06-25

# BETA Records - Privacy Policy

**Overview**  
This Privacy Statement covers the website, www.betarecords.com, which is owned and operated by BETA Records, LLC a California Company (BETA Records we or us). Your data will be maintained by BETA Records in accordance with this Privacy Statement. Your privacy is important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet enjoyable and to foster your trust in us as a whole. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users' privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices.

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of our website and the services offered to you and, cannot in any way, be separated from the User Agreement or from the membership, usage or transaction process. If you do not agree to our Privacy Policy in whole, you must not use our website.

**Member Registration Information**  
When you become a BETA Records member you provide your name, address, telephone number, email address, birth date, gender, a unique login/email name, a stage name, password, and various categories of musicianship information (i.e. song and picture uploads, genres, instruments, career, etc.). This information is collected on the signup form for several reasons including: (1) personal identification; (2) to complete your member profile registration; (3) to allow us to contact you for customer service, if necessary; (4) to customize the content of our website to meet your specific needs; and (5) to make product improvements to www.betarecords.com In addition, your email address is collected to send you an email message confirming your new member registration and future changes to your account. If you provide a fax number, you may receive faxes confirming your signup and other online transactions. As a member you will occasionally receive email or fax updates from us about special offers, new www.betarecords.com services, and other noteworthy news items. However, you may always decline to receive these email and fax messages. Please see our Opt -Out policy described below.

**Member Profile Information**  
As a BETA Records member, you can choose to complete, update or change your online profile by logging in to your profile page using your chosen username and password in the My BETA space. Some profile information is made public and can be reviewed by visiting your respective member profile page. The information is made public to assist you in showcasing your music, pictures and personal biography and by providing the public a way to make contact with you via telephone, email, 3rd party website, etc. It is important that our Members study their entire profile page and understand that this information is public to visitors of www.betarecords.com.

**Opt-Out**  
To keep you in control of your personal information and the communications directed to you, we allow you to opt-out of receiving certain communications from BETA Records about new features or services. If a guest objects to such use for any reason, you may stop that use, either by email request to [privacy[at]betarecords.com](mailto:privacy@betarecords.com%20title=) or by modifying/deleting your member information online.

**Invitations and Communications to non-Members**  
BETA Records members can invite friends to view their artist profiles by sending invitation emails via our automated invitation system. BETA Records stores the email addresses that members provide to send reminders of the invitations. BETA Records does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Recipients of invitations from BETA Records may contact BETA Records to request the removal of their information from our database at [privacy[at]betarecords.com](mailto:privacy@betarecords.com%20title=).

Members of BETA Records may also store email addresses of people they know (friends and fans) in their internal BETA Records address book and may also choose to send communications to those addresses.

You may prevent BETA Records email invitations and other messages from being sent to any email address you control by sending a single email with the subject text of BLOCK to [privacy[at]betarecords.com](mailto:privacy@betarecords.com%20title=). Please note that the email must contain the exact email spelling of the account you wish to block.

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Use of Traffic Data**  
Each time a visitor comes to our Web site, we collect some information to improve the overall quality of the online experience. At the Web site, we collect the visitor's domain name (i.e., where the user is logged on, such as from Yahoo.com, etc.), referral data (e.g., we record the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to the BETA Records Web site), and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform). We collect visitor information for purposes of product monitoring, product improvement, and targeted advertising. We also count, track, and aggregate all visitors' activity into our analysis of general traffic flows at our sites (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the BETA Records pages, etc.). To these ends, we may merge information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregated basis with our advertisers; but BETA Records will not disclose your individual identity or personal data without your permission. When BETA Records does present aggregated information to outside companies, no one is able to identify you or contact you.

**Use of IP Addresses**  
An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you're surfing the Web. Web servers, our centralized computers that 'serve up' web pages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

BETA Records collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregate, or combined, information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When users request pages from the BETA Records Web site, our servers log the user's IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that your session will be logged, but you remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a user when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our rules or terms of service or to protect our service, site, customers or others.

**Use of Email Data**  
BETA Records will use your e-mail address to send correspondence about password changes and confirmations, important updates about our website. Members, who sign up to receive BETA Records' newsletters, will receive a BETA Records content newsletter delivered either on a monthly basis, as well as occasional special announcements.

Users can choose to unsubscribe from BETA Records newsletters or product-related announcements at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions found in each e-mail or by contacting [privacy[at]betarecords.com](mailto:privacy@betarecords.com%20title=).

BETA Records offers contests in which we request certain personal information. At a minimum, the required information includes name and e-mail address; in some cases, the user must answer survey questions about a range of other personal data. The information gathered in the entry form is used to verify the entrant's identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients. Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. There are two situations in which BETA Records will divulge this information to a third party: (1) A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest sponsor, in which case the user's personally identifiable information is divulged to the advertiser; (2) Some of the contests may be hosted on the BETA Records site but administered by the sponsor; in such cases, the information a user provides is passed on to the third party.

**Surveys**  
Occasionally BETA Records conducts user surveys to better target our content to our audience. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any personally identifiable information with such third parties.

**Links to other sites**  
Users should be aware that when you are on BETA Records, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. There are links to other sites from BETA Records pages that take you outside our service. For example, if you click on a banner advertisement or a BETA Records artist profile page, the click takes you off the BETA Records site. This includes, but is not limited to, links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use BETA Records' logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

BETA Records' policy does not extend to such third parties' use of such information, anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond BETA Records' control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Profile Pages, Chat Rooms, Blogs, Message Boards, and Classifieds**  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information on your Artist Profile page, to Chat rooms, Blogs, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other BETA Records public forum that it can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.

**Children**  
In accordance with the COPPA Act, we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

**Security**  
BETA Records has taken strong measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored. We take strong precautions to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

The importance of security for all personally identifiable information associated with our guests is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, BETA Records cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. When credit card information is transmitted we use industry standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. SSL is a coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble data before you send it to us.

Unfortunately, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. Therefore, although we will endeavor to protect your privacy as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will remain private.

Your BETA Records account is password protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. BETA Records will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or e-mail. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information.

**Sale of assets, Mergers, Acquisition, Bankruptcy**  
Information collected from you may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale or acquisition, merger or bankruptcy involving our Company.

**Your acceptance of these Terms**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the BETA Records Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites. Your continued use of the BETA Records Web site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting to the BETA Records Web site.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted on this page. We encourage you to check the last update date on this page regularly. Your continued use of the Site following any changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. You agree that the information that we gather now will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

**Contacting the website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact [privacy[at]betarecords.com](mailto:privacy@betarecords.com%20title=) or write to;

BETA Records, LLC  
Attn: [legal[at]betarecords.com](mailto:legal@betarecords.com)  
1350 N. Highland Ave.  
Hollywood, CA 90028 

_Last updated August 18, 2010_
